[{"answer": "Giddy? Err ... well, I personally prefer professionally excited I think I said, excited to be here General. I haven't been giddy since ... well you wouldn't want to know about that", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah, don't you think she's nice", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Look I really don't have time ... I've got ... errr ... briefing", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "The Prometheus incident, I know the air force insisted on their own crew", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Just a job. I consider it my job to put you up on a pedestal because this Job looks to me nothing but to be extraordinary and from what I read from you file the same can be said about you personally", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Boring. Good odds. my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "that place's disqualified for being a smartass. I'll go with two headed aliens", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why what", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't know, you'd have to ask her", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yes we're trying our best And senator don't take this the wrong way but it sounded a bit prepared like a speech I don't think you'll like the results. What if we do it off the cut, I throw things at you see how you respond ..", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No ..", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No ... If you want anything else from me ..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No I didn't know that", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well, did you tell them about the time that you tried to get this place shut down or the time you had my friend by the short ..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh, sure ..", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Makes sense", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, what's the difference then, why not shoot it and decide later", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Not up to me ... not up to me ... that's great", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "ah ... Dr. my friend ... H", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "oh ... you're packing ... you're going on a mission off ... I'm sorry I forgot the expression ..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Off world", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No ... Nope just ... err going through my pack", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "*grin", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "See that's the thing ... when there is action ... I'm too busy to be pointing a camera ... You know ... I'm running, shooting, trying to get back that kind of thing ..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Mmmm ... are you ... err ... flirting with me", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Heroes-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "*Laugh", "qsentId": 28}]